<resources>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_app_name">SampleApp</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_button">Go to Fragment\'s sample Activity</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_fragment_hello_world">Hi I\'m inside a Fragment :D</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_fruits_description">Apples and pears. Citrus – oranges, grapefruits, mandarins and limes. Stone fruit – nectarines, apricots, peaches and plums. Tropical and exotic – bananas and mangoes. Berries – strawberries, raspberries, blueberries, kiwifruit and passionfruit.</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_veggies_description">Vegetables are parts of plants that are consumed by humans as food as part of a meal. The original meaning is still commonly used and is applied to plants collectively to refer to all edible plant matter, including the flowers, fruits, stems, leaves, roots, and seeds</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_grains_description">A whole grain, also called a wholegrain, is a grain of any cereal and pseudocereal that contains the endosperm, germ, and bran, in contrast to refined grains, which retain only the endosperm. As part of a general healthy diet, consumption of whole grains is associated with lower risk of several diseases.</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_dairies_description">Milk products are a type of food produced from or containing the milk of mammals, primarily cattle, water buffaloes, goats, sheep, camels, and humans. Dairy products include food items such as yogurt, cheese, and butter.</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_proteins_description">Proteins are essential nutrients for the human body. They are one of the building blocks of body tissue and can also serve as a fuel source. As a fuel, proteins provide as much energy density as carbohydrates</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_nuts_description">A nut is a fruit composed of an inedible hard shell and a seed, which is generally edible. In general usage, a wide variety of dried seeds are called nuts, but in a botanical context "nut" implies that the shell does not open to release the seed</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_sweets_description">Candy, also called sweets or lollies, is a confection that features sugar as a principal ingredient. The category, called sugar confectionery, encompasses any sweet confection, including chocolate, chewing gum, and sugar candy. Vegetables, fruit, or nuts which have been glazed and coated with sugar are said to be candied.</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_fries_description"> Deep frying is a cooking method in which food is submerged in hot fat, such as cooking oil. This is normally performed with a deep fryer or chip pan, and industrially, a pressure fryer or vacuum fryer may be used. Deep frying is classified as a dry cooking method because no water is used. Due to the high temperature involved and the high heat conduction of oil, the food is then prepared quickly.</string>
    <string name="core_mvp_sampleapp_soft_drinks_description">A soft drink is a drink that typically contains carbonated water, a sweetener, and a natural or artificial flavoring. The sweetener may be a sugar, high-fructose corn syrup, fruit juice, a sugar substitute, or some combination of these.</string>
</resources>
